[Music]
good morning Prudential this is a
greeting UTA Prudential always because
here in Prudential it is always morning
weather afternoon or evening it is
always morning we draw our energies from
the energies that the morning provides
full of sunshine full of brightness and
strength and dedication to achieving the
targets that are ahead of us that's why
we want you to choose potential in the
industry you're joining one of the
fastest-growing agency forces
eversince potential entered the market
in 2014 to date we are one of the
largest agency forces in the country we
run a unique agency model that supports
you as an agent give you the chance to
have a career path unachieved a true
greatest objective of any agent to
attain status and make money to look
after themselves and their family in
Prudential we produce a career path to
make you successful this career path
gives you the opportunity to move up
from a team leader after you dedicated
yourself at excelled as an agent to
sales on its own we'll give you the
chance to build a team not only that you
can climb up from a team leader up to an
agency manager and even an agency
director in Prudential you're joining a
worldwide brand which encompasses 26
million clients said by 30,000 agents
across four continents and backed by
26,000 employees this is a worldwide
brand that you become a part of and
that's all we are inviting you to be a
part of the family in here gives you as
much support as you can our sole aim is
to make sure that we help you first as
an agent to find your feet and to give
you the right skills you require to kind
of up the ladder to become a successful
leader all our agents here are there to
help you as part of the broader family
to help you settle in when you join
Prudential to the new agents who are
just joined us our message to you is
threefold
number one focus focus on your jaw focus
on the Huddle's
focus on generating process
after you focused on these things add to
them the ability to produce we help you
with the skills to produce produce as
many cases as possible and then show
that of all these cases that you produce
as many of them have their clients
paying for them to become inseparable
eases if you focus on these three
principles you will be successful
as an agent and then you'll be able to
achieve your dreams of becoming a
successful Neda with multiple lines of
income to achieve your dreams of a
higher status and more income to look
after yourself and your family
welcome to the family once again we all
exist to support you remember at
Prudential we are always listening and
always understanding welcome once again